Guide to the Wells Rich Greene Inc. Records, 1954-1998 and undated RL.01365
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1954-1998 and undated (Acc. 98-0396), 140 boxes
  - Video and Film
    - Liberty Mutual Insurance (continued) (Box 45)
      - 29. 8 spots-- Master. 1991. TRT: 4:00 (Box 45)
      - 30. Night Driving Revised 2. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 45)
      - 31. 5 spots + Avoiding Collisions w/ questions. 1992. TRT: 2:15 + 16:08 (Box 45)
      - 33. 9 spots. 1992. TRT: 4:30 (Box 45)
      - 33A. (Duplicate of #33). 1992. TRT: 4:30 (Box 45)
      - 34. Repetative (sic) Motion. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 45)
      - 35. 4 spots. 1992. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 45)
      - 36. 6 spots. 1992. TRT: 3:00 (Box 45)
      - 37. Window Rev 4. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 45)
      - 38. Repetitive Motion Rev-- Master. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 45)
      - 39. Avoiding Collisions with Questions Rev.-- Master. 1992. TRT: 16:08 (Box 45)
      - 40. Kennametal Fleet. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 45)
      - 41. 2 spots-- Master. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 45)
      - 42. 3 spots-- Master. 1993. TRT: 1:30 (Box 45)
      - 43. 6 spots (with :03 seconds black between each spot). 1994. TRT: 3:15 (Box 45)
    - Liberty Mutual Insurance (continued) (Box 46)
      - 44. 6 spots. 1994. TRT: 3:00 (Box 46)
      - 45. Kelly's Introduction. 1994. TRT: 6:00 (Box 46)
      - 46. Teen Driving Rev. 2. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 46)
      - 47. 6 spots. 1995. TRT: 3:00 (Box 46)
      - 48. 2 spots (both Legend Tune in). 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 46)
      - 49. Tune In ABC. 1996. TRT: :15 (Box 46)
      - 50. LM Focus Group Edit Jan '95. 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 46)
      - 51. 2 spots (both Legend Tune-In Rev.). 1996. TRT: :30 (Box 46)
      - 52. Client Vers. Only--4 spots. 1996. TRT: 2:30 (Box 46)
      - 53. Client & Agency. Vers.--7 spots. 1996. TRT: 4:00 (Box 46)
      - 54. Client Old Logo--6 spots. Circa 1996. TRT: 3:30 (Box 46)
      - 55. 5 spots. 1997. TRT: 3:00 (Box 46)
      - 56. New Logo--8 spots. 1997. TRT: 3:00 (Box 46)
      - Liberty Mutual Competitive. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 46)
    - Liquicil (Miles Labs)
      - 4. Stand-up III Revised. 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 46)
      - 5. 5 spots. 1977. TRT: 2:30 (Box 46)
    - Love Cosmetics (Box 47)
      - 1. 16 spots. 1975. TRT: 8:00 (Box 47)
      - 2. 3 spots. 1976. TRT: :30 (Box 47)
      - 3. Daisy-L Revised. 1970. TRT: :30 (Box 47)
      - 4. Daisy-L (old version). 1975. TRT: :30 (Box 47)
    - Max Factor
      - 1. Composite Reel (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 47)
      - 2. Master Reel 2 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 47)
      - 3. Master R-3 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 47)
      - Is She Real--2 spots. TRT: :40 (Box 47)
      - 61. 6 spots. 1986. TRT: 3:00 (Box 47)
      - 62. 7 spots. 1986. TRT: 4:00 (Box 47)
      - 63. Le Jardin--Jane Seymour / Espris--Jackie Smith. 1986. TRT: 1:00 (Box 47)
      - 64. 6 Spots. Undated. TRT: 3:00 (Box 47)
      - 65. Light & Natural / Hooray for Hollywood. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 47)
      - 66. 2 spots-- (both Luscious Lips/ New). 1986. TRT: 1:00 (Box 47)
      - Max Factor Reel--Ken Olshan (list enclosed--8 spots) 1991. TRT: Circa 4:00 (Box 47)
    - May Company-- May Company National Pool #1 (laVers)
      - 12 assorted spots (list enclosed). Undated. TRT: Circa 10:00 (Box 47)
    - MCI Communication Corp. (Box 48)
      - 1. MCI Mail--2 spots-- (both Now..). 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 48)
      - 2. Corporate--12 spots (list enclosed) Master. 1987. TRT: 4:15 (Box 48)
      - 3. Corporate--MCI Account Rep/ Comptroller. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 48)
      - 4. Corporate--6 spots. 1987. TRT: 3:00 (Box 48)
      - 5. MCI--3 spots. 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 48)
      - 6. International Service.--2 spots. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 48)
      - 7. MCI International--2 spots. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 48)
      - 8. International--Bear Rev. Hello / Africa Rev. Help. TRT: Circa :15 (Box 48)
      - 9. MCI--6 spots. 1988. TRT: 4:00 (Box 48)
      - 10. MCI--The Traders. 1988. TRT: :15 (Box 48)
      - 11. MCI--9 spots. 1988. TRT: 4:30 (Box 48)
      - 12. MCI--9 spots. 1988. TRT: 3:00 (Box 48)
      - 13. MCI--Clocks Master. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 48)
      - 14. Residential--16 spots (list enclosed) Master. 1988. TRT: 8:00 (Box 48)
      - 15. Long Distance--Test Drive-Revised Master. Circa 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 48)
      - 16. Long Distance--High Performance--Revised. Circa 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 48)
    - MCI Communication Corp. (continued) (Box 49)
      - 17. MCI--3 spots. Circa 1988. TRT: 1:30 (Box 49)
      - 18. Corporate--Hall Rev. 1. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 49)
      - 19. Card--Truck Rev II. 1988. TRT: :15 (Box 49)
      - 20. Corporate--Hall Rev. 2. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 49)
      - 21. MCI/FAX--3 spots. 1988. TRT: 2:00 (Box 49)
      - 22. fax--6 spot. 1988. TRT: 2:45 (Box 49)
      - 23. MCI--Multi-Reel (23 spots--list enclosed). 1988. TRT: Circa 12:00 (Box 49)
      - 24. FAX no music--6 spots. 1988. TRT: 2:45 (Box 49)
      - 25. MCI--The Office Manager. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 49)
      - 26. Corporate--5 spots. 1988. TRT: 1:45 (Box 49)
      - 27. Corporate / Prism Plus--Why / Rev. II. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 49)
      - 28. Corporate--2 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 49)
      - 29. FAX--2 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 49)
      - 30. Corporate--Ladder of Success / AR Open. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 49)
      - 31. 1989 Corporate--Herska / Western Europe-Rev. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 49)
      - 32. Corporate--Ladder of Success / Rev. (Acct. reps). 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 49)
    - MCI Communication Corp. (continued) (Box 50)
      - 33. FAX Network--2 spots. Circa 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 50)
      - 34. MCI--2 spots. Circa 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 50)
      - 35. MCI--Hour Glass. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 50)
      - 36. MCI--Pay Phones. 1989. TRT: :15 (Box 50)
      - 37. Corporate--Ring, Ring/ Rev. (800 Service). 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 50)
      - 38. Residential--Pay Phones Rev. 1989. TRT: :15 (Box 50)
      - 39. MCI--The Traders 89. 1989. TRT: :15 (Box 50)
      - 40. Operator Assistance--Call Collect Give Em. 1989. TRT: :15 (Box 50)
      - 40A. Corporate--Call Collect. 1989. TRT: :15 (Box 50)
      - 41. 4 spots. 1989. TRT: 2:00 (Box 50)
      - 42. 800 Service--Telemarketing Exec. Window. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 50)
      - 43. MCI International--2 spots. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 50)
      - 44. Corporate--Bill McGowan Heritage Intro. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 50)
      - 45. CAS, Prism Plus, 24 hr. Customer Service--3 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:30 (Box 50)
      - 46. Call USA--2 spots (both Herska /. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 50)
      - 47. Corporate / Call USA--2 spots (both Herska-. 1989. TRT: 2:00 (Box 50)
    - MCI Communication Corp. (continued) (Box 51)
      - 48. Corporate / Call USA--2 spots. 1989. TRT: 2:00 (Box 51)
      - 49. Corporate--2 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 51)
      - 50. Corporate--2 spots. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 51)
      - 51. Residential--14 spots (list inside). 1989. TRT: 7:00 (Box 51)
      - 52. Corporate--3 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:30 (Box 51)
      - 53. Corporate--8 spots. 1989. TRT: 3:00 (Box 51)
      - 54. Corporate--4 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:45 (Box 51)
      - 55. MCI Corp.--2 spots. 1990. TRT: :45 (Box 51)
      - 56. MCI-Call Europe--9 spots. 1990. TRT: 4:30 (Box 51)
      - 57. MCI--3 spots. Circa 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 51)
      - 58. International Calling--Call Korea Tradition Rev. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 51)
      - 59. International Calling--3 spots. 1990. TRT: :45 (Box 51)
      - 60. MCI--2 spots (both Babies/Non-New). 1990. TRT: :45 (Box 51)
      - 61. MCI--6 spots. 1990. TRT: 2:30 (Box 51)
      - 62. Corporate--2 spots. 1990. TRT: :45 (Box 51)
      - 63. Call USA--3 spots (all Herska/Rev.). 1990. TRT: 3:00 (Box 51)
    - MCI Communication Corp. (continued) (Box 52)
      - 64. MCI--3 spots (all Grandpa). 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 52)
      - 65. Prime Time--3 spots (all Grandpa Rev.). 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 52)
      - 66. Prime Time--2 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 52)
      - 67. Prime Time--3 spots (all Torpedo. 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 52)
      - 68. MCI- 3 spots (all Call.Rev. 1). 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 52)
      - 69. MCI Communications--3 spots 9 all Eating). 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 52)
      - 70. Call USA--2 spots (both Herska/..RCirca). 1990. TRT: 2:00 (Box 52)
      - 71. MCI International Calling--5 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:45 (Box 52)
      - 72. MCI--Bert Roberts / Heritage. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 52)
      - 73. Agency Version--3 spots. 1990. TRT: Circa 1:30 (Box 52)
      - 74. Primetime--2 spots. 1990. TRT: :45 (Box 52)
      - 75. Primetime--2 spots (both Torpedo). 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 52)
      - 76. Primetime--4 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:45 (Box 52)
      - 77. Primetime--3 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:15 (Box 52)
      - 78. Premier World Calling Plan--2 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 52)
      - 79. MCI Vision (Use for Agency Reels) --6 spots. 1990. TRT: Circa 2:50 (Box 52)
    - MCI Communication Corp. (continued) (Box 53)
      - 80. Vision--8 spots (on-air version). 1990. TRT: 3:30 (Box 53)
      - 81. Vision--Presentation to Sales Force w/ Countdown. 1990. TRT: 5:33 (Box 53)
      - 82. MCI Communication--Cassoulet Rev. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 53)
      - 83. Residential--12 spots (list enclosed) Master. 1990. TRT: 6:00 (Box 53)
      - 85. MCI--3 spots multi Master. 1990. TRT: 2:00 (Box 53)
      - 85. Residential--3 spots. 1990. TRT: 2:00 (Box 53)
      - 86. Residential--3 spot (list enclosed). 1990. TRT: 7:00 (Box 53)
      - 86. Residential--3 spot (list enclosed) Master. 1990. TRT: 7:00 (Box 53)
      - 86. Residential--3 spot (list enclosed). 1990. TRT: 7:00 (Box 53)
      - 87. Residential--4 spots Master. 1990. TRT: 2:00 (Box 53)
      - 88. Residential--2 spots (both Savings alt./ …). 1990. TRT: Circa 1:00 (Box 53)
      - 90. Residential--Clown. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 53)
      - 91. MCI--2 spots Master. 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 53)
      - 92. Corporate--Helmet (Tom Landry). 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 53)
      - 93. MCI--8 spots. 1990. TRT: Circa 4:00 (Box 53)
      - 94. MCI--4 spots. 1990. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 53)
    - MCI Communication Corp. (continued) (Box 54)
      - 95. Rip-O-Matic--2 spots. 1990. TRT: Circa 1:00 (Box 54)
      - 96. Rip-O-Matic--Competitive. 1990. TRT: :40 (Box 54)
      - 97. Rip-O-Matic--Vision. 1990. TRT: :45 (Box 54)
      - 98. Primetime (sic) --Grandpa (Agency Version). 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 54)
      - 99. MCI--1988Historical Reel--27 spots. 1990. TRT: 11:30 (Box 54)
      - 101. MCI--1988Historical Reel--27 spots. 1990. TRT: 13:30 (Box 54)
      - . MCI--Vision--7 spots multi 7 spots. 1991. TRT: 3:05 (Box 54)
      - . Compilation Reel--15 spots. Undated. TRT: 6:00 (Box 54)
    - Michigan Opera Detroit
      - Rehearsal--2 spots. 1980. TRT: 1:00 (Box 54)
    - Midas International
      - 1975. Midas 1975 commercials--7 spots. 1975. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 54)
      - 1976. Midas 1976--8 spots. 1976. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 54)
      - 1990. Midas International 1990 TV Availability Reel (3/19/90) (Compilation Reel--Circa 109 spots (list enclosed) ). 1990. TRT: Circa 45:00 (Box 54)
      - 1990. [Midas International Reel #1--Super Version--37 spots-- final color correction & legals Pre-Convention (list enclosed). 1990. TRT: 10:30 (Box 54)
      - A. Midas International Brakes--2 spots. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 54)
      - B. Midas International Brakes--Speed Bumps. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 54)
      - #1. Midas Master Reel 1 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 54)
      - #2. Midas Master Reel 2 (35 spots--list enclosed). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 54)
    - Midas International (continued) (Box 55)
      - R3. Midas Master R 3--Midas Historical--42 spots. 1975. TRT: 27:30 (Box 55)
      - R4. Midas Master R 4. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 55)
      - R5. Midas 86 Campaign Master Reel 5--16 spots (list enclosed). 1986. TRT: 6:20 (Box 55)
      - R6. Midas Master R 6. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 55)
      - R7. Midas Master R 7. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 55)
      - R8. Midas Master R 8. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 55)
      - R9. Midas Master R 9. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 55)
      - R10. Midas Master R 10. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 55)
      - R11. Midas Master R 11--63 spots (list enclosed). 1993-1994. TRT: Circa 22:00 (Box 55)
      - R12. Midas-- Master Reel 12--Circa 73 spots. 1993-1995. TRT: Circa 30:00 (Box 55)
      - 1. Midas--Guarantee Creety (original). 1976. TRT: 1:00 (Box 55)
      - 15. Muffler/ Shocks--2 spots. 1978. TRT: 1:00 (Box 55)
      - 17. Foreign Car Mufflers--7 spots. 1978. TRT: 3:20 (Box 55)
      - 36. Mufflers--9 spots. TRT: 4:20 (Box 55)
      - 59. Midas International--16 spots along with Creety Message Film (list enclosed). 1986. TRT: 7:20 (Box 55)
      - 71A. Midas International--2 spots. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 55)
    - Midas International (continued) (Box 56)
      - 77. Midas--1990 Campaign--Final 1990--34 spots. 1990. TRT: 10:20 (Box 56)
      - 82. Midas--Brakes--9 spots. Undated. TRT: 3:15 (Box 56)
      - 85A. Midas International--3 spots Master. 1992. TRT: 1:30 (Box 56)
      - 94. Brakes--31 spots (all Baby) (list enclosed). 1992. TRT: 10:05 (Box 56)
      - 124. Suspension--4 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:20 (Box 56)
      - 125. Midas International Brakes--Randy Terwillinger. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 56)
      - 126. Midas International Brakes--Randy Terwillinger Revised. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 56)
      - 127. Midas--16 spots (list enclosed). 1994. TRT: 6:30 (Box 56)
      - 127A. Midas International--Letters 1994 Campaign--15 spots. 1994. TRT: 6:00 (Box 56)
      - 128. Midas--2 spots. 1994. TRT: :45 (Box 56)
      - 129. Midas--2 spots. 1994. TRT: :45 (Box 56)
      - 130. Midas Intl--No Prices / Credo. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 56)
      - 131. Midas--2 spots. 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 56)
      - 132. Midas International Corp--2 spots. 1994. TRT: :45 (Box 56)
      - 133. Midas International Mufflers--8 spots. 1994. TRT: 2:15 (Box 56)
      - 134. Midas International Mufflers--3 spots. 1994. TRT: :35 (Box 56)
    - Midas International (continued) (Box 57)
      - 135A. Midas International--9 spots. 1995. TRT: 4:00 (Box 57)
      - 136. Midas--10 spots. Circa 1995. TRT: 5:00 (Box 57)
      - 137. Midas--Linda Kaplan Thaler--Gag Reel. Circa 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 57)
      - 138. Midas--4 spots. 1995. TRT: 2:15 (Box 57)
      - 139. Project Safe Baby PSA--Loving Mother. 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 57)
      - 140. Midas Brakes--Dear Foreign Car Owners Rev. 1995. TRT: :15 (Box 57)
      - Misc. 26. WRG--Midas Muffler $1.99. 1974. TRT: :30 (Box 57)
      - Misc. 34. WRG--Midas Ski--Version A. 1975. TRT: :30 (Box 57)
      - Misc. 43. Midas International Midas Shocks--4 for 3. 1976. TRT: :30 (Box 57)
      - Misc. 46. Midas 1976 TV Commercials--8 spots. 1976. TRT: 4:00 (Box 57)
      - Misc. 47. New Book--Midas Muffler Presentation Reel. 1970-1975. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 57)
      - Midas Mufflers--6 spots (see also Box 122WRG 115 for Midas Case History). 1983. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 57)
    - Merit
      - Master Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 57)
    - Miles Labs
      - Core C-500, Dub-- (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 57)
    - Mobil Oil Company
      - 1. Mobil Master #1 (#'s 1-19, 21-45) (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 57)
      - 2. Mobil Master #2 (#'s 46-53, 66-56) (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 57)
    - Mobil Oil Company (continued) (Box 58)
      - 4. Hefty--2 spots (both Wimpy). 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 58)
      - 4A. Hefty--Mainstream. Circa 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 58)
      - 38. Hefty Cinch Sak--2 spots (both Amber). 1989. TRT: :45 (Box 58)
      - 39. Hefty Cinch Sak--3 spots (all Second Best). 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 58)
      - 52. Hefty (Cinch Sak) --3 spots. 1990. TRT: :45 (Box 58)
      - 62. Hefty Kitchen Twist Tie Bags--2 spots (both Forming Box/R). 1992. TRT: :45 (Box 58)
    - Mobil Land Development
      - 1. America's New Homes--2 spots. 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 58)
      - 3. Mobil Land Meeting Final. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 58)
      - 4. Mobil Land--Revisions to come. 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 58)
      - 6. Mobil land Dev.--Where Dreams Live (Windward). 1995. TRT: 4:00 (Box 58)
    - National Enquirer
      - Master Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 58)
    - Neo-Citron (Miles Labs).
      - #1. Neo-Citron--Copycat. 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 58)
      - 2. Miles--7 spots. 1977. TRT: Circa 3:10 (Box 58)
      - 3. Neo-Citran (sic) --Copycat. 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 58)
    - [New York: see box 59] (Box 58)
    - Noxell
      - 1. Morning Light Cologne--2 spots (both Morning Light). 1977. TRT: 1:00 (Box 58)
      - 2. Morning Light Cologne--Morning Light (Dialogue) Rev. 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 58)
    - New York State Dept. Of Commerce (Box 59)
      - 1. Tourism--3 spots (all Tourism). 1977. TRT: 2:00 (Box 59)
      - 2. Tourism--6 spots. 1977. TRT: 4:30 (Box 59)
      - 3. Tourism--Broadway 1978. 1978. TRT: 1:00 (Box 59)
      - 4. I Love New York--3 spots (all Broadway). 1978. TRT: 2:00 (Box 59)
      - 6. NY State Dept. Of Commerce--2 spots (both Broadway). Circa 1978. TRT: 1:00 (Box 59)
      - 7. I Love Broadway Show Tour--People, Places & Things. 1978. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 59)
      - 8. NY State--I Love NY Broadway Show Tour--CBS News 2/14/78--Good Morning America: Dragoti/Tiegs. 1978. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 59)
      - 9. NY State--I Love NY Broadway Show Tour--NBC-NY 6o'clock News--Report on Theater Campaign's Success. 1978. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 59)
      - 10. NY Tourism--I love NY Theater NBC-NY 6 o'clock news. 1978. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 59)
      - 12. NY Tourism--4 spots. 1978. TRT: 1:00 (Box 59)
      - 13. I Love NY--I love NY New Audio--no voice cover. 1978. TRT: 1:30 (Box 59)
      - 15. NY State Tourism--2 spot (both Canada). 1978. TRT: 3:00 (Box 59)
      - 16. Tourism--4 spots. 1978. TRT: 1:00 (Box 59)
      - 17. Business--2 spots (New Hampshire). 1978. TRT: 3:00 (Box 59)
      - 18. NY City Theater--4 spots (Dracula). 1979. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 59)
      - 19. Tourism (City Weekend) --I love NY Show Tours 79--2 versions. 1979. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 59)
    - New York State Dept. Of Commerce (continued) (Box 60)
      - 20. Eye Witness News--Joel al reports on New I Love New York Commercials and Regine's Party. 1979. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 60)
      - 21. Tourism--3 spots (all Love NY at Night). 1979. TRT: 2:00 (Box 60)
      - 22. Tourism--3 spots (all Love NY at Night). 1979. TRT: 2:00 (Box 60)
      - 23. Tourism--3 spots (all Love NY at Night). 1979. TRT: 2:00 (Box 60)
      - 25. Tourism--2 spots (both Love NY at Night in French). 1979. TRT: 1:30 (Box 60)
      - 26. Eastern Airline--5 I Love NY In-flight Commercial. Circa 1980. TRT: 1:00 (Box 60)
      - 28. Tourism--3 spots (all Events-). 1980. TRT: 1:30 (Box 60)
      - 29. Tourism--2 spots. 1980. TRT: Circa 1:00 (Box 60)
      - 30. NY State--3 spots. 1980. TRT: 2:00 (Box 60)
      - 31. Department of Commerce Kodak Film. 1980. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 60)
      - 31A. I Love NY--Kodak Footage I Love N.Y. Master. 1980. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 60)
      - 32. NYS--6 spots for 6 airlines Master. 1980. TRT: Circa 3:00 (Box 60)
      - 33. I Love NY--5 spots titles enclosed. 1980. TRT: Circa 2:30 (Box 60)
      - 35. Tourism--Surprises--9 spots (all Surprises--list enclosed). 1981. TRT: Circa 4:30 (Box 60)
      - 36. NY State Co-op Footage--United Airlines Passenger Service; I Love New York--Leo Burnett USA. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 60)
      - 37. Tourism--I Love New York at Night / Sills Rev. (French/ Canadian Ver.). 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 60)
    - New York State Dept. Of Commerce (continued) (Box 61)
      - 38. Master--Surprises/Scotsman (French Canadian Ver.). 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 61)
      - 39. NYS Dept. of Commerce--3 spots (all Surprises/ Canadian). 1981. TRT: 2:00 (Box 61)
      - 40. Saturday Night Live. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 61)
      - 41. Tourism--Razzle Dazzle/Promo. 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 61)
      - 42. NYS Dept. of Commerce--Products. 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 61)
      - 42A. Business Development--Products alternative version. 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 61)
      - 43. Business Development--Companies. 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 61)
      - 44. Business Development-- 2 spots. 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 61)
      - 45. Business Development--Taxes Rev. 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 61)
      - 46. Tourism--3 spots (all Razzle Dazzle). 1981. TRT: 2:00 (Box 61)
      - 47. Tourism--6 spots (all Razzle Dazzle Canadian Ver.). 1981. TRT: 4:00 (Box 61)
      - 48. Business Development--Products Rev. 1981. TRT: :30 (Box 61)
      - 49. Tourism--Razzle Dazzle/Liz (French Canadian Ver.). 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 61)
      - 50. Business Development--4 spots. 1982. TRT: 2:30 (Box 61)
      - 51. Tourism--Razzle Dazzle/Promo Rev. 1982. TRT: 1:00 (Box 61)
      - 52. Business Development-- 2 spots. 1982. TRT: 1:00 (Box 61)
    - New York State Dept. Of Commerce (continued) (Box 62)
      - 53. Tourism--Foreign Intrigue/US Ver. 1982. TRT: 1:00 (Box 62)
      - 5. Tourism--6 spots (all Foreign Intrigue/). 1982. TRT: 4:30 (Box 62)
      - 55. Tourism--2 spots (both Foreign Intrigue in French. 1982. TRT: 1:30 (Box 62)
      - 56. Business Development--Working Heroes. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 62)
      - 57. Business Development--Working Heroes Rev. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 62)
      - 58. Council on the Arts--4 spots (all Kitty Carlisle Hart). 1982. TRT: 2:00 (Box 62)
      - 59. Business Development--Working Force. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 62)
      - 60. Business Development--Working Force. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 62)
      - 61. MINY Business Development--Taxes Revised Logo. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 62)
      - 62. Business Development--Todd Products Logo Rev. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 62)
      - 63. Business Development-- Companies Rev. Logo Fortune500. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 62)
      - 64. City Vacations/Tourism--9 spots (list enclosed). 1983. TRT: 6:00 (Box 62)
      - 65. Tourism/City Weekends--2 spots (both Broadway Rhythms (French Canadian) ). 1983. TRT: 1:30 (Box 62)
      - 66. Tourism/City Weekends--Broadway Rhythms (French/ Canadian) ). 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 62)
      - 67. State Tourism--2 spots (both See New York). 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 62)
      - 67 (again). Tourism--3 spots (all See New York) US Vers. 1983. TRT: 2:00 (Box 62)
    - New York State Dept. Of Commerce (continued) (Box 63)
      - 68. Tourism/ Upstate--6 spots (all See New York). 1983. TRT: 4:00 (Box 63)
      - 69. NYS Tourism--See New York US Version Master. 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 63)
      - 70. Tourism--2 spots (both See New York Canadian Vers). Circa 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 63)
      - 71. Tourism--6 spots. Circa 1983. TRT: 4:00 (Box 63)
      - 72. Tourism--6 spots. 1984. TRT: 4:00 (Box 63)
      - 73. Tourism--4 spots. Circa 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 63)
      - 74. Tourism--2 spots. 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 63)
      - 75. Tourism--2 spots (both../Buffalo). 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 63)
      - 76. Tourism--2 spots (both / Canadian English). 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 63)
      - 77. Tourism--Wilderness--Rev. /French Canadian Ver. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 63)
      - 81. Summer 1985 Tourism--2 spots. 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 63)
      - 82. 6 spots (all Star). 1985. TRT: 3:00 (Box 63)
      - 83. Summer Tourism--Beachcomber USA. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 63)
      - 84. Summer Tourism--8 spots. 1985. TRT: 4:00 (Box 63)
      - 85. Tourism--2 spots. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 63)
      - 86. Tourism--2 spots (revised 0f 85). 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 63)
    - New York State Dept. Of Commerce (continued) (Box 64)
      - 87. Tourism--2 spots. 1986. TRT: 1:00 (Box 64)
      - 88. Tourism--Lights French Master. Circa 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 64)
      - 89. Tourism--If I Could See. Circa 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 64)
      - 90. Tourism--If I Could See-Fun. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 64)
      - 91. NY State Tourism--2 spots (both If I Could See). Circa 1986. TRT: 1:00 (Box 64)
      - 92. City/ Tourism--2 spots. 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 64)